The He Manor is located
in a prime spot in Rongcheng.
It's isolated from the world,
and ordinary people can hardly enter.
Today
happens to be Master He's 60th birthday,
which is why you temps were hired.
Later on,
every one of you better be on high alert.
Are you crazy?
These clothes were made according to
the sizes you registered.
Did you eat too much for lunch?
Let me tell you,
these clothes
are made of imported Italian fabrics.
Are you okay?
Can you afford to pay for it
if you ruin it?
If you were official employees
of the He family
and dared to break the rules,
you'd be dead meat.
Look alive, everyone.
Come to me for your pay after the banquet.
It's been 17 years.
I'm finally home.
I am actually Mr. He's
biological daughter,
He Mei, the heiress
of Rongcheng's richest man.
But now I can only return
as a temporary nanny.
To those who once wronged me,
how have you been?
You are not official employees
of the He family,
so you don't have names.
Next, I will call you
by the numbers on your chests...
Let me assign your tasks.
Numbers one through five,
you're in charge of greeting guests
and assigning tables.
Numbers six, seven, and eight,
you'll run food from the kitchen.
No sneaking food.
Numbers nine and ten,
go to the wine cellar.
Once the banquet starts,
except for numbers one through five,
no one else is allowed in the inner hall.
Is that clear?
Understood.
Try and hide.
Keep hiding.
I'll go get another one.
You clean up first.
This check
is your reward.
Let me go.
Let go.
Woman,
you've successfully caught my attention.
Young Master,
I've noticed you for a long time too.
How dare you...
I thought you liked it, Young Master.
Interesting.
Please behave yourself, Young Master.
Does a poor person like you
want to marry another poor person
and have a bunch of poor kids,
or just give in to me?
If you have any brains,
you'd make the right choice.
I may be poor,
but I have my dignity.
Let go.
Nobody says no
on He Shi's turf.
Let go of me.
Let go.
Mrs. He is awake.
Everyone gather to see Mrs. He.
Let go of me.
Why are we still missing one person?
Where is Number 10?
Number 10.
Coming.
What Number 10?
Hello, Mrs. He.
Dismissed.
Mrs. He,
you look beautiful today.
time for your foot bath.
Isn't that Zhang Xin,
the He family's head maid?
Why is she acting like Mrs. He?
Yeah.
I can't believe she has the eldest
daughter-in-law washing her feet.
But I've heard
the eldest daughter-in-law doesn't come
from a good background either.
So this is what life
in a wealthy family is like.
How are the preparations for
the Master's birthday banquet going?
Madam He,
everything is proceeding smoothly.
That
That is.
The assembly was called ages ago.
Where have you been,
looking like such a mess?
Madam He,
just now the Eldest Young Master...
Liu Dan!
Yes.
You can't even manage a temp worker.
Nothing can go wrong
at the Master's birthday banquet,
or I'll make you pay.
Yes.
Go change your stockings.
All the villains
are gathered here.
Go away.
Mom.
Brother.
Let me out!
You killed my mother
and sold me deep into the mountains.
Do you know how hard it was for me
to make my way back here
over the past 17 years?
From today on,
I will be every single one
of your worst nightmares.
The banquet starts in ten minutes.
One, two, three, four, five.
I can't find a single one of you inside.
What are you dawdling for?
Hurry up.
Do you want your pay or not?
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't you know your own number?
You are 10, not 01.
The kitchen is out of wine.
Go fetch some from the cellar.
Hurry up.
So clumsy.
I have to get inside the banquet hall
so I can see my dad
and reunite with him.
You idiot.
Honey,
I'm sorry.
I told you to prepare
a birthday gift for Dad,
and you got this junk?
Come here.
Honey.
Honey,
I'm sorry.
Honey.
Get in here.
Please,
don't do this.
Is it that hard to ask you
to do one simple thing?
Honey,
no.
Stop.
Come on, get up.
Why is it you again?
Young Master,
Master He will be back soon.
Butler Liu asked you to go downstairs.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
Do you need to go to the hospital?
I'm fine.
Are you the new temp?
What's your name?
Li Zhangxin.
Could you please
get some ointment from next door?
Mei, this is for you.
Thank you.
Could this be He Yu?
How did he
end up like this?
Thank you.
Is that the second young master, He Yu,
in the next room?
How could he...
Yes,
he's my brother-in-law.
He was in a car accident
three months ago.
But Mr. He
didn't want anyone to know,
so he suppressed the news.
Please,
you must keep this a secret.
Okay.
Why isn't there a caregiver?
I've been taking care of him.
Is there no one else?
Is he really that neglected at home?
Mr. He is here.
I finally get to see
the richest man in Rongcheng.
Is he good-looking?
Yes, he is.
Here, Master.
Master,
Dad,
This is
Fu tea from our hometown in Shaanxi.
Thank you all for doing me the honor
of attending my birthday banquet.
I believe you have all heard,
due to my
deteriorating health,
I have decided
today...
To announce
the heir to the He family.
But
unfortunately,
I cannot make this decision for now.
This is because
my biological daughter, He Mei,
is still missing.
Over the years,
I've gone through untold hardships
to find her.
Today,
taking the opportunity of my birthday...
I pray to heaven
that my daughter, He Mei,
will return soon.
Yes, yes.
She'll return
soon.